#### Contact

deepmind0207@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/antonio-davis-81a44a24a (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Ruby on Rails Elixir React.js

# **Antonio Davis**

JavaScript / Ruby on Rails developer

Wanze, Walloon Region, Belgium

## Summary

I am a seasoned engineering manager and full-stack developer with 6+ years of experience in software engineering primarily working on RoR, and JavaScript frameworks.

I have solid expertise in building web applications, data pipelines, advanced reporting and analytics systems, and data science functions for different domains like payments, fintech, telecom, and utilities.

I also have relevant management skills, having built and managed a small team with 3 - 5 members.

## Experience

Sigasi

React / Ruby on Rails expert February 2022 - Present (9 months)

Ghent, Flemish Region, Belgium

Experfy (Harvard Innovation Lab) https://www.experfy.com/

The Experfy platform enables the pipelining and hiring of external talent at unprecedented speed, while career pathing, upskilling, and mentorship of your internal talent. License our self-service platform or hire SME-vetted talent from our TalentClouds.

Full Stack RoR project. Database: PostgreSQL

I had developed Frontend and Backend using Ruby on Rails.

Hodope

Senior Software Developer

Thesis Technologies
JavaScript / Ruby on Rails expert
June 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 5 months)
Namur, Walloon Region, Belgium

ebooks Network https://www.scribd.com/

Scribd gives you access to millions of ebooks, audiobooks, magazines, podcasts, and more — all in one place, for one price.

Frontend: React , Backend: Ruby on Rails, Database: PostgreSQL

There, I took part in developing backend using Ruby on Rails.

Steel Marketplace Felux https://www.felux.com/

Felux was established by a group of steel and technology experts with one mission – create the world's largest operating platform and marketplace to help solve commerce for the steel industry

Frontend: React , Backend: Node.js, Database: MongoDB There, I took part in developeind Frontend using React.

#### Cardify

Ruby on Rails Developer March 2018 - May 2020 (2 years 3 months) Ghent, Flemish Region, Belgium

EZOfficeInventory https://ezofficeinventory.com

EZOfficeInventory is one of the Leading cloud-based asset-tracking software. It provides features for work orders, maintenance, purchase orders, and label scanning. This product is used by Microsoft, Amazon, Stanford University, Netflix, ICC, and many others.

There, I worked as a Full Stack developer.

### Education

University of Liège
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (September 2011 - September 2015)